Lon!
Lon… Wake up…
Ship’s log:
After all these years,
finally, it’s time.
You know what you need to do.
I have to get hold of
the Map of the Hakuru…
but Zak will never allow it.
You are the Great Zorn!
Get up!
I need Cloe’s help…
You do not need anyone!
Follow the plan...
and you’ll have more power
than you ever imagined!
I will be with you.
I’ll never suffer again.
I’ll never have to be alone.
The multiverse will be at my feet!
Lon!
Zak!
Cloe!
Am I dreaming?
Or was that a giant Zorn Meka
kidnapping Cloe?
Kiet! Fenzy!
Zak!
What’s going on?
Did you throw a Zorn party
without inviting us?
It's Lon! And he’s got Cloe!
I told you this “dating” thing
would end in tears!
Let's get to the hill!
Wait! The ships are moving!
We’ve got to get to the hill!
Didn't I just say that?
Human "Cloe,"
welcome to your suite.
Suite?
This isn’t a hotel,
it’s a prison!
The Great Zorn wishes you
a pleasant stay.
Hey, wait!
Let me out of here!
What the... ?
A map of the ship…
And a route leading me to another room…
But how do I get out?
OK...
Now I just need a source of Sen energy.
Someone wants to play games.
Then let’s play!
SEN-DO-KAI!
Buckle up, Lon! I’m gonna…
Bye-bye, Cloe.
Now what?
Zak? Can you hear me?
Cloe! Are you OK?
What’s going on?
I’m fine, I’m fine! But listen…
Someone on the ship
is helping me!
What?
It’s a trap! It's gotta be!
I have to find out what’s happening.
You’re on board a Zorn warship!
It’s too dangerous!
We already took out
one of those hunks o' junk.
They have a weak spot!
The Sen storage tanks.
Yeah, if we hit the generator…
we can cut off
the whole ship’s energy supply!
But how do we find the ship?
With the map of the Hakuru!
If we know where Cloe is,
we know where the ship is.
Gotcha!
Great!
I’m going to solve this mystery!
We’ll cut off the energy supply!
And then I’ll deal with Lon…
Follow me!
Hang in there, Cloe!
We're coming!
We’re going in through those doors.
Cover me and I’ll blast ‘em wide!
Zap!
Oh wow, amazing plan.
OK, Miss Negativity,
anything constructive to add?
Yeah: why do we always
have to do what you say?
Because I am the Hakuru!
Humans!
Look out!
We gotta strike back!
But we don't have any dös!
I know where to get some!
Cover me!
Koa Sen Shield!
Tai Sen Trail!
Human guest!
You may not leave your suite!
Worst. Hotel. Ever.
I'll be talking to your manager.
This way…
See, Kiet?
This is what you call style!
It’s kinda samey though?
You need some fresh moves.
Geo Sen Shockwave!
Ka-boom! Match that!
OK, let’s ramp the cooliosity
up to the maximosity!
Zet Sen Shot!
Go Sen Tornado!
Yeah!
Bim, bam, boom!
Look at that,
Miss Negativity here
just saved your butt.
OK, OK! Let’s get inside!
There it is!
The generator!
Piece of cake!
We are numerically superior.
Please consider surrender.
Sure, we accept: you can surrender!
My apologies,
what I intended to say was…
OK guys, cover me
and I’ll blast it apart - Zap!
That’s the same plan as before.
And it still sucks!
Leave this to me,
it needs more bim-bam-boom!
No, no, no.
What it needs is just a little bim...
and then KABOOM!
What are you two talking about?
There’s only one way to decide this
democratically, equitably and fairly…
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
This is it.
Ship’s log: Stardate 210403.
I have deciphered
the ancient scroll of Beldzar.
Danima planted five seeds
of pure Sen energy
on five planets
scattered across the multiverse.
I travelled to each planet
and found only devastation.
Four have been destroyed,
and the Sen seeds stolen…
Only one remains - Earth.
But they are coming.
Beings with the most destructive powers
I have ever seen.
The Yitsu.
The only hope of defeating them
is the Stardö.
To activate it, I need the seed
from planet Earth.
And now, I know where it is hidden
Inside the map of the Hakuru.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
Zak. I've got something!
Lon wants your map,
the map of the Hakuru!
Right! Everybody wants to be the leader!
Why would that idiot be any different?
No, Zak, there's more, and it's bad!
The Yitsu are coming,
to take the Sen seed!
The what? The “Yitsu?"
The Sen seed?
Zak? What’s wrong?
Nothing… I’m fine.
Cloe! This is all coming
from Lon!
You know he’s a liar!
Zak, Lon hurt us,
he betrayed us,
but he never lied to us.
Thank you for believing in me, Cloe.
Lon!
Cloe, are you OK?
Can you hear me? What's happening?
Kiet, Fenzy! The job’s yours!
Don’t let me down!
-I’m just going to call dibs.
-Oh man!
Yao Sen Vision!
Impressive.
But the show's over.
Lon! What are you doing?
Let me out of here!
You're a monster!
No. I am the Great Zorn!
And when I have activated the Stardö
I will rule the multiverse...
With you at my side!
That’s never going to happen!
And Zak will never give you the map.
Zak is a fool,
and he will give me the map
because I have the best possible bait.
-You.
-No...
Lon... what happened to you?
I have become more powerful
than you can imagine!
Maybe... but you're still alone.
No! What are you doing?!
Nu Sen Flare!
Don’t try anything, Lon!
Cloe... Cloe! It's me!
It was me who helped you escape...
How am I supposed to believe you?
Who are you really?
The helmet gave me power.
I became the Great Zorn.
But one day everything changed.
I had a dream, and it was so real.
In the dream, there was a message for me:
"Find the Stardö."
And Cloe… I found it.
-So it's true....
-Yes. When the Stardö is activated
my army will be so powerful
I'll be able to defeat the Yitsu!
But then why kidnap me?
I need you to help me,
to convince Zak to give me the map.
Why should I trust you?
There’s one more thing....
It was in the message...
“Tell Cloe, she chose
the wrong train.”
How do you know that?
I never told anyone.
You have to trust me.
Cloe?
What… what’s going on?
Here we go!
Watch and learn, Kiet!
Ha! This is how you do it.
Proceed to eliminate them.
Looks like we upset them.
We gotta to defend ourselves!
No! I’m sick of playing defense.
We need to attack!
I’ve got it! Kiet: you and me,
we’ve got a connection, right?
Yeah, sure.
Then let's try something new.
OK! Let's do a…
Duo Sen Force!
DUO SEN FORCE!
More power, Fenzy!
Coming up!
-Gotcha!
-Check us out!
Uh, when I said we had a connection,
all I meant was...
-No, no, me too, I'm not like...
-Phew!
Put it there, Fenzy!
Did we take it up a notch too far?
What's going on?!
Zak, listen...
Cloe! Stand back!
And you - get away from her!
You have to give him the map.
What?
I am the only one who can open it.
The power of the Sen seed
would kill any normal human.
A normal human? I'm the Hakuru!
If you want my map,
you’ll have to rip it out of my hands!
It would be absurd to fight.
I have an Empire!
That Empire's not looking
too sturdy to me.
No!
The generator has failed...
But how?
Kiet? Fenzy? You did it!
Maybe even overdid it!
We have to get out of here!
See you outside!
Those guys…
It’s causing a chain reaction
across all systems.
The ship's going to explode!
You need to go!
Now!
-But Lon...
-Cloe!
You guys!
-Over here!
-The ship's going to explode!
Zak!
No!
We're going to be squished!
Lon!
You saved us...
I saved the map.
“The map of the Hakuru!"
Ha! It is so much more than that…
OK, this is totally insane!
The greatest power in the multiverse,
from the beginnings of time,
the Sen seed!
Now all I need is the final piece…
It’s the Stardö.
The what now?
At last!
It works!
Now I will be unstoppable!
Lon! This isn't you!
Take off the helmet!
Never!
This is the pure power of the Sen,
and it's mine!
What?
If you won't take off that helmet,
I'm going to do it for you!
I'll crush you!
Not bad,
Zak's got some new moves after all!
Sho... Sen...
Fire!
How's that crushing thing
working for you now?
You fool! All I wanted
was the stupid map!
Now I'm going to have to destroy you.
Ha! It must suck so much to know
you'll never be as cool as me!
You're nobody, and your story ends here.
That’s where you’re wrong, bud!
This is just the beginning!
Zet... Sen... Shot!
You took everything I had!
But you're not going to take this!
The power of the Sen must be mine!
You want power, you spoilt little brat?
Here, have some power.
You did it, Zak!
Mission accomplished...
At last, a time out.
I take it back!
What's going on?
The Stardö - it's out of control!
It's going to explode!
Are you guys OK?
I feel like I was hit by a truck.
Our armor, our powers...
It's all gone!
It was the Stardö. Lon!
What happened? What do we do now?
It's over.
The Yitsu will come. And without my army,
no one can stop them.
I failed.
Lon, you didn't fail.
You brought the Stardö.
Ha. You'll never be able to use it.
You don't stand a chance.
Good luck, guys.
Lon, you're an arrogant jerk.
And I should know,
because I am one too.
I get way too full of myself.
I should listen to my friends.
And sometimes my plans aren't the best.
In fact, I have no clue
how we're going to stop the Yitsu.
But I know we can do it.
Because we never give up...
...and that's the spirit of Sendokai.
Right.
We’ve had our backs against the wall 1000 times,
but we always come through.
Yeah! And we always have
a blast along the way.
And we do it all
for the people we care about most.
OK.
But just to be clear.
I don't need any motivational speeches.
And I don't need your friendship.
But nobody can face this on their own.
Remember...
A Sendokai warrior is never alone...
...as long as they have a team.
Sen-do-kai!
Senkuns!
This is only the beginning!
Sendokai Champions season 3
is coming soon!
And you want to be ready
when it does, right?
So, make sure you subscribe!
And in the meantime,
watch the first two seasons!
Absolute cinema.
The Stardö has awoken.