Ahh! Nothing like a
hearty supper with friends!
You know what would go down a treat now?
A little nip of quondam juice!
none left
Zhu Li mistook it for a bottle of water
and dragged a lot
Teenage passion when you hold me tight!
Teenage passion! [mumbled speech]
Looks like it's gone straight to her head
So what do we do?
We could tell stories!
Good idea!
Who! do you want to start the ball rolling?
Bowling?
Do I want to go bowling?
Oh, nevermind
Grum why don't you tell us the tale of
the Sendokai Warriors who saved the
multiverse!
Why not?
It all began many moons ago
The Zorn empire was
conquering the multiverse
And drawing ever closer
to a planet named Earth
Which was home to four youngsters
Chloe, Kiet, Fenzy, and Zack
They were what you call popular
Go on! Get lost!
But one day something
happened that would change
their lives forever
Sendokayetus!
Tampo, the Wadan, accepted them as
his Senkuns and sent out to turn them
into Sendokai warriors
To save their planet from the Zorn invasion
They would have to win
The Great Sendokai Tornament
And so, their training began
In the urlock dimension
Where they helped the inhabitants
fight off giant cockroaches
Hooray!
In return, The Urlocks gave them their
first suits of armor
Sen-Do-Kai!
Tampo continued working
them hard to improve their abilities
Sometimes, Tampo organised combats
against other Sendokai warriors
To put his Senkun's skills to the test
They even had to compete against
The guardian of Nustrad's chest as they
Oh yes!
Good pooch!
As trained and learned
to control the sen energy
They traveled to new dimension and
made new friends!
Chloe helped the Maoons and their fight against the
hidden ones
And discovered her Yao-Sen vision
Kiet liberated the Morlocks dimension
and activated his Coa-Sen Shield
Fenzy fought alongside the beldzars
That was the first time she used the
Tai-Sen trail
Gotcha!
And Zach defended the Kaijuns
from the Senadompt attack
He finally mastered the Zet-Sen shot
That boy has something special about him
Although he couldn't beat me
laughs
Sure, and the fact he
slipped on your glass-eye had
nothing to do with it, right?
A- minor detail
As I was saying, they
liberated many dimensions!
But the night before the tournament,
Tampo revealed a secret
He told them- I'm a bearded woman!
No! That's not what he said!
He didn't? I must've gotten
it mixed up with another story
The "bearded-woman" business was something
that happened to me it was a little
embarrassing
what did tempo tell
Them that he had competed
in the great tournament 10,000
years earlier! And lost! and so condemned
his people to slavery
At last, the day
of the tournament dawned and the
youngsters fought like real warriors
Tai-Sen Trail!
They faced opponents of all shapes and sizes
each stronger
than the one before
Each more dangerous
but the Senkuns had new armor
And new powers
Zack had activated the Sho-Sen Fire
Chloe the Nu-Sen Flare
Young Fenzy could unleash the
Go-Sen Tornado
And Kiet, the Geo-Sen Shockwave
all these different attacks are making
my head spin
as the tournament progressed the story
took a new turn
Lallith, we'll always be together the
Lallith was my girlfriend
And, well Tampo
and Lallith were not the only ones who
felt a special feeling
Blow it and make a wish!
Aww, how sweet
But the toughest part was still yet to come!
They still have to face the
Zorn commanders!
First they fall against Cascrad's
Team, who turned out to be
Dark versions of themselves
The humans won, and defeated their own
dark side!
Next, they faced commander Lallith and her team of specters
Lallith was about to
defeat the youngsters
But at the very last minute
something unexpected happened
the commander let herself be beaten so
So that tanpo and the Senkuns could
defeat the Zorn
Treason!
To punish her betrayal,
The Marshal condemned Lallith to the vortex
But Tanpo stepped in to
save her!
And at that moment
He revealed before the whole world
The marshal's real identity
Kento is the one who was
once my brother
That I was not expecting
In the end, Tampo sacrificed himself to
protect the woman he had always loved
The youngsters were on their own
The last Sendokai would take place on
earth as the invasion began
But those young warriors weren't gonna
stand by and let it happen that
Lallith joined them and together they made a
plan to defeat the Zorn
The final of the tournament arrived and
things looked bleak
The Zorn were too strong
only a miracle can save us
But then
Tanpo returned from the vortex
Bringing reinforcements
Tt seemed there was still hope
Sho-Sen Fire!
Until the marshal played his final card
The marshal transformed the Senkuns
into normal children
No!
And their wristband stopped working
I once told you: to be
a Sendokai warrior...
Is much more than wearing a wrist band
Forward, Senkuns!
Yours, Fenzi!
The youngster summoned
up their coverage and
faced the Marshal
And in that very moment, Zack remembered
his real motivation
And that was how a bunch of kids from
Earth saved their planet
And the rest of the Multiverse!
Aw, happy endings always make me cry
Poke your eye?
I did not poke your eye!
...not this time
But, did Sid Modi's managed to escape?
Yes
At the last moment he grabs a strands chest
and things got even more complicated!
But that's another story
What?! You can't leave us hanging
What about Zack and Chloe!?
Did they own up to their feelings?
What about Tanpo and Lallith?
What happened to them?!
And Kento? What happened to Kento?
You can't end the story like that!
We need to know more!
Calm down!
The story doesn't end here
But it's late. You'll find
out what happened next
very soon