[Music]
ah
[Applause]
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [
Music]
come on today is not happening today are you going to ask
cloud to go to
the cinema with you
[Music]
he
you can't play with bulls  from ghana
like normal cats
low
[Music]
hurry up you don't want to be late the
first day of class it's going it's going well it's
eggs in the fridge we have to
take your sister to the pediatric hospital since she was
born ona it seems like you're overlooking me
that's not true
[Music]
what was your name fed sad
I'm leaving being an older brother requires
as much responsibility as being an
interdimensional warrior
I once saved the earth you know and now
he changed diapers
you're looking forward to starting the first
day of school of course although  I really
want to finish it more. Well, in
fact, that's what I wanted to talk about. I
was thinking. Do you do something this
afternoon because if you want, we could go to
the movies together. Great. I
thought you were never going to ask me.
Well, I found two
tickets on the street.  yes, sure
[Laughs]
[Music]
ok what's up, god, go to school, do you
remember when we did missions and
save, let's go to Peña Arciga, it was cool, well, there
's nothing more than with Ian. I don't know how to
go to the movies, yes, I guess now our
mission  is to become responsible people
s
more than being a good warrior or the handles we
can't say anything about them you know
warriors guys a little silence
please I want to introduce you to your
new classmate his name is long
[Music]
his family has just  get to the city
so I hope you treat it well you can
sit there
and very well on this first first day I am
delighted
i
[Music]
and my name is tak I introduced myself before
but you didn't hear me we are going to
play a little game and I was
wondering  If you wanted to sign up, look at the
pace of your little game and yes, I
heard you but I didn't feel like saying hello.
Hey, if you don't know how to play, it's okay, but there's
no need to be rude, of course, I
could beat you up. If not, you
'll have to see how much  you want
[Music]
and [ __ ] detector is about to
explode
[Music]
you weren't going to go to the movies with Chloe it's going to
be late it will only be a moment
[Music] [
Music]
things
and them [Music]
[Music]
[Music  ]
does that have been
what the hell
well
my friends told me
[Music]
we have to stop what I run
from 106
[Music]
good [
Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
I can't leave them alone for even a moment
this city is  very strange what the heck was
that
a me here a spirit without sen we have
bad news the minister moved and
disappeared when the fortress
thorne exploded no no
before the fortress exploded
sign of the cyclone to nyad they got the
cesc box back
and the other thing
There, yes, no, God is using the box to
absorb the sen of its inhabitants and
become stronger every time he
absorbs energy without means, his victim
becomes a journey
and how he got here we still don't
know, somehow the Yaquis
are  entering the earth let's go
no
nothing I'm not you
no ago who are you the retreats have
had the destroyer or I will have td
eliminated
[Music]
very good you have wanted it
as it seems very destroyer
calm there is no danger you are on
planet earth they have been transformed into  a
yak and the land I have to return to my
village you will return but I need you to take
these warriors with you you are you
have to find mobius like this and
snatch the ses box back and only
you can get it
chrome 5th
have these will be your new
bracelets
[Music]
every
what is this, take it out of me too and two
with them you
know too much besides I have seen you
fight against the me here you are fast and
cunning it is a joke I am not sorry but I will not
follow the orders of a goblin if it is
better that you do not come
these missions are dangerous
[  Music]
so in that case you will need someone to
watch over you
okay to accept
I guess we're not going to go to the movies right
not today but don't worry I'm sure
I'll find more entries well guys what do you
think if instead of becoming
responsible people  we become
warriors in tokai
of this crown
being streets
[Music]
without a place a new adventure begins
and
ah [
Music]
[Applause]
[Music]