Great shot master. I swear
your aim gets better every day!
That is enough Sidmodius
a level one Yaki is sufficient
I want more energy
You must use Sestrad's chest in moderation
until you can control it
I need to be stronger!
so how do we get to this new
dimension Tanpo was talking about?
Ask him. That's where he's from.
Take me to your leader! I demand an explanation
I have modified the portal.
It will now transport you
to the dimension where
Kronum-Yatt, My sister is.
Be careful! I know Sidmodius
and He will do anything
to prevent you from
destroying the chest!
He will have many Yakis
to protect him. Remember:
To defeat them. You must
strike their energy centers.
You mean, you're not coming?
No. We have another mission. There is something mysterious about this whole affair. And I want to
investigate but you must not be afraid. Or Sindo chi warrior is never alone. As long as they have a team
Hold out your arm and yell send Yo Kai
right
my body it's changed
it's the wristband you'll get used to it
Welcome to my planet
guys, look
the sorne fortress
looks like it transported here before it exploded.
Is that thing yours? You humans have no idea how to park a ship.
And what's that?
The home of Dan Nima High Priestess of the center this is where my brothers Keenan and keyway we're doing this send a chi training is the priestess.
You have sent a chi here to of
course, to the people of Massara. Nothing is more important than send a chi. We resolve all our conflicts on the field.
Well, you're in luck because the king of Send okay just rolled into town
oh yeah well in the school yard yesterday the king of Shindo chi stood there like a statute Good thing I reacted in time
I did not just stand there I was a headwind
maybe this team needs a leader with better reflexes Did you hear that
I recognize that smell it's it's
aim for their heads
looks like that's not gonna do it
not their heads
remember to defeat them you must strike their energy centers
you got to hit them in their energy center fenzi surround them with a Tyson trail.
What are you talking about?
Benzie
keep shooting
Tyson
Chloe what's their next move gonna be
yeah
the one in the middle is going to jump kit. I need a platform
said saying shocked
yes
they're getting away
good work
oh, it's an old lady. Oh, High Priestess.
Where are your manners? It's done NEMA on your knees.
Uh, who are you? What happened to me?
We are sendo chi warriors from Planet Earth. You got turned into a yucky.
I remember. We were training when this ship fell out of the sky. We went to investigate. And we were hit by someone whose heart was full of darkness.
Said modius.
I priestess. The other Yankees with a
yes. Your brother's? Hey,
don't sweat it. We'll find them. Even if we have to search the whole of Massara.
If that is your intention, you will need help. Which of you is the Haku rule. Who is the leader of this tea? Is it you? Or you?
I think it's me.
In that case, take this activated
It is a matter of Massara as her quarrel, it is your responsibility to carry it and guide the others. A hawk who must always remain with his team, through good times. And through bad. Thank
you. We'll give Sid modius what he deserves.
You must be careful. The Yankees you have seen so far, we're not especially powerful. But Sid modius will grow stronger. Creating higher level Yankees.
Don't worry. ascendo codewarrior is never alone. As long as they have a T
shirt humans Why must they always interfere? Relax, great master. I bet it's just a coincidence
Don't worry about the humans. I sent a Yaquis to Earth to attract their attention.
And why did you do that? They
to a part of the plan.