So, you're saying we're
this little mark here?
Right
And this red guy's a Yaki.
And if we follow the Yaki's
trail. He'll lead us to Sidmodius.
Cool!
Yeah. You can tell he's the Hakuru
Although, it's not totally accurate
Don't worry.
It looks like Kido can
follow a trail too...
Or... something
We're on the right track!
Oh, yeah.
This is all great and everything, but
Is it much further?
According to the map, the
Yakis shouldn't be...
Right here
Wow! This is worse than my bedroom!
Hey guys. Check this out
Isn't that the helmet the
marshal war during the final?
Yeah.
The great Zorn's helmet
Uh oh
Looks like we found our friend
He's close by! I can feel it!
I don't understand!
What's wrong?
The Yakis should be right here
Hit his energy center!
Where are you going, you one-eyed ape!
Quick, follow him!
Alright, we're ready to go!
What's wrong, Tanpo?
I had a premonition.
I think the youngsters are in danger.
I'm sure they are
They're Sendokai warriors.
But you shouldn't worry about them.
Because thanks to you, they're the best.
You're right! There's no time to waste.
We must discover why
Sidmodius has gone to Massara.
And where will we do that?
Where all the knowledge
of the multiverse is stored
In the great tower of
the Beldzar dimension.
But isn't that where-
Yes, Lallith. That is where he is.
I lost him! He's not on the map!
Well, that least we still have
the iguana with a mohawk
Kido, what are you doing?
Have you ever seen a Yaki attack a coconut?
No.
Precisely if the Yakis think I'm a
coconut I'll be able to sneak up on them
unnoticed
And attack!
Hey, Zach!
What you said about going to the movies?
Is that still on?
yeah yeah sure
great because it would be a shame if we didn't get to go out on our date
I'm not going to let you escape
wow I that's right yeah key
I'm not going to let you escape what were you saying nothing Forget it though don't move
is it a Yaquis now it looks like a smiley face
Hey, I see him there's a red dot and another and another
it's an ambush attack
we need more dose
coconut
that yucky I think he's level two
yeah I don't see any difference
sin
okay so he's different
high priestess the other yakkers with a yes your brothers
Cana key way it's made Kido your brother you crazy lizard we just want to help you guys
out this is bad
kid behind you
know guys retreat
don't scare me let's go I'm almost got I said let's go
Are you okay? Sure. There's nothing You're a coward. We could have beaten them. It was too dangerous.
I'm not going to risked my friends lives for nothing. Or yours
What happened?
Three Yaquis surrounded us. One of them was level two.
I see them you will have to be stronger. I will train you. I will show you the most powerful techniques ever seen on Massara.
I don't believe it. The Sorcerer's suffer said herself is going to train us
that yaki is going to learn not to mess with yet. Oh
stay calm. Go home now. You will need to rest this is only the beginning
good work my weakest. This is the time to crush those humans. Forget them. I would ask that question. First, you must grow stronger. He will travel Massara destroying every village in your path and absorbing all the energy of the inhabitants
I'm starting to like this planet