[Music]
ah
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] [
Music]
Dad, I'll be back later today, let's
go, but I haven't played piano for five years, I've
met up with some kids from school, they
're not bad, they're really nice, tender  long I'm going
to give you some advice it's okay to hang out
with people but I don't trust them nobody
gives anything without looking for something in
return not even friendship
it must be horrible to be afraid of
everyone thanks to that I've come this far
[Music]
everything is fine  You are very serious, we had
agreed to make a few touches, you could
have come by to help you stop
Ximo, God does not mean that he is your
friend, what
you say, aunt
[Music]
everything in masada is connected, every
petal, every drop of water,
every living being
[Applause  ]
and I am connected to the planet I
can feel its energy
but also its suffering every time
without modus it turns someone into a yak
and
[Music]
the Yaquis that you have seen are nothing
compared to those who are to come let them come I sing
how
much  The more energy I take from them without
hatred, the more energy you will have to
give back to them so that they can recover their
original state and how are we going to gather so much
energy, one warrior cannot,
but two can, as long as they join their doors
with this
[Music] [
Music]
iu armor
[Music]  ]
and
no
[Music]
why are
we going
[Music]
the armors have a transmitter testing
hello hello
every kilo coming here [
Music]
point the bracelet at your partner's chest
how
[Music]
you feel each other's energy
yes
no convoys in them
[  Music]
now try to release the force 2 in
and it is in them
we take
[Music]
nothing happens you simply have to
work on rapport the more
connected you are the more energy you can
add it
is time to make a separate kai
[Music]
we will fight against each other
stop
everyone
[Music]
7 s local
look
[Music]
well [
Music]
sorry let's
use force
and now
[Music]
and I don't
and
[Music]
no maybe they will trust me a little more
this wouldn't happen
[Music]
take it
[Music] we
don't have to be friends if you don't
want to but you have to trust
us I can't trust one well it
must be horrible to be afraid of everyone
[Music]
I stay
shots
[Music]
it's useless wow  cheap crib
there is a rock being waiting for us
[Music] we
are going to release that power
[Music]
[Music] [
Music] [
Music]
here
and in Canada
[Music]
and strong they have gathered so much energy that
a single fall was enough for them
[Music  ]
well you bought guys well this aunt
thanks
[Music]
well
today
what is happening
without modus she has just attacked a village and has
turned its inhabitants into Yaquis and
we have to return those Yaquis to their
original state
or China
will die
[Music]
we will find  to those Yaquis and
we will free them
from animal news the village that
your home
[Music]
miseries
good
[Music]
and
[Applause]
[Music]