Quick Hurry up. My people need help
you know, my SIR is giving me a really familiar feeling. Yeah,
it's called being tired. I get that on Earth too.
Hey, Keith keto. Is it much further? No,
we have to cross that plane of hard luck it's a little desert
he would only take three days come on don't just stand there kiddo
we can't walk through a desert for three days
we'll get dehydrated.
Do what I do make your own sweat very well if you prefer we could use these that skimmers the drivers left them here when they completed their training with Dyneema
you have to charge them up with your own energy
guys is it just me or is this good a total Euro
you key down the destroyer is about to make mincemeat of you. You think I could drive
it's okay I got it. You can get
some rest don't you trust me?
Core site trust you
Hey guys, last one to the paper rock is a loser
teach go any faster
the face to me.
No fetal weight
tadpole the wild lolly. Welcome to the great tower of bells. How can I help you?
Your Majesty. Suit odious is still alive and has traveled to a dimension named Massara.
We had never heard of this place before. And we do not know why Sid modius has gone there.
We have come in search of answers.
Then you have come to the right place described I have worked for you,
Your Majesty. That day you offered me sanctuary. I swore loyalty to you and to this library. It will be my pleasure to help you. Thank
you, but it is not for myself. I ask. I wish you to help our guests. lollies and your brother tampo
Hello canto
gram sorry Your Majesty but I am afraid I can do nothing for them if tiempo needs to consult the library he can do it himself
oh no this is horrible Hello
Hello Is anyone there father son modius has turned them all into Yankees and he's taken them with him
I don't think they've gone look at the footprints
We're surrounded
I say cool
let's use the judo same force
there's not the weekend do
coward
we go
yes
Chino now was arch chance
to do Yes
Father What are you doing with my crown Who were you? They friends of mine.
They friend you
did die really? By gradient prepare a banquet for our honored guests. What
you clumsy Oh, even as a servant, you're a failure. And you say the seed mode is transformed us all. I don't believe it. It must have been those yellow bellied grow beards Shall
I think it was the car tax nonsense. It was the film's Michelle rose crawling with those creeps now Now stop
it. You're wasting time fighting amongst yourselves. When you should be standing together. Besides Ketos not clumsy. He fought alongside us. He helped release you all. Tito
don't make me love. The only thing he's ever released is gas. We call him Kido de sticker if only he was the Yaquis no is brothers keto. Pull me another drink? No,
I've had enough. What? I'm going to save Kenan a key way of proof that I too, am fit to be a warrior.
You can't go who do the cooking.
Get your crown to do it
well said, Dude you want to drive?
What was I think? You're right. There is something familiar about Massara. It's almost like we've been here before
the moon have you found something.
And the gods of the sun filled the sky with clouds. And when their work was done, they created the sun and the moon. This was the origin of Massara long before the dark Genesis, long before it became known as Planet Earth.
By all the gods fit modius and the youngsters didn't travel to another dimension. They traveled in time.
Exactly. Massara is Earth in the past