Alright. I'm going to the
movies with Cloe today.
I'm going to the movies with Cloe today!
I'm going to the movies with Cloe
I'm going to the movies.
You can't go anywhere today.
You have to stay home
with your sister.
Your father and I are going out for
dinner tonight. Don't you remember?
Oh, no.
Yes? Oh hey, Zak!
I'm about to leave.
What's wrong?
Well, I think we're going to
have to cancel on the movies
What? Again? Why?
I have to babysit my
sister I didn't remember.
I'm sorry.
No, no. Don't worry.
It's not your fault.
See you tomorrow.
How do you cook this?
Wait a minute.
Pizza? Yes, I know how to do it!
Perfect!
No, no, no, no!
Ona, be careful!
Close one!
They're calling us
But I can't leave you alone!
Zak and Lon have managed to
control The Duo-Sen Force into
an attack power. But
Sendokai, it's not all attack.
Kiet and Fenzy
You must unleash a defensive power.
The Duo-Sen Wall
If anyone knows how
to stop a do, it's us!
Yeah!
Now some former disciples of mine
will come so you can practice with them.
What happened to Zack?
He couldn't come.
He had to-
I'm here. Look.
Zak!
Well, well, well.
So you couldn't leave the house
because you had to look after your sister.
Yeah, well, the truth is.
You've got a bug on your back!
Get away from me.
I'll kill it.
Don't worry.
Hello, little one.
How cute.
Guys, meet The Grubers
Hello, priestess.
It's been a long time.
Grubers! Formation!
To survive in Masara, The Grubers
became geniuses of technology.
Attack formation!
Relax, guys. We'll activate The
Duo-Sen Wall And we'll defeat them.
There's only one who can defeat
a druber!
Another Druber!
No. Don't move from here, okay?
Sen-Do-Kai!
This will be a two-kai fight.
Let the Sendokai begin!
Duo-Sen Fury!
Kai!
Oh, no.
They're very strong.
A Gruber, always wins
the fights he enters!
And the ones he doesn't, too
What's going on?
She's attacking me!
584! 584!
I need backup!
Ona!
Zak
Either you take care of your sister
or you fight with us.
But it can't be both.
Excuse me.
Lon! Let's get this over with.
Duo-Sen Force!
Ona!
Kai!
If you can't take fighting
seriously, you shouldn't have come.
Kiet! I think those squirrels
are eager to try our medicine.
Duo-Sen Fury!
Duo-Sen Wall!
Wow
We did that.
Lon! Now we can use
the Duo-Sen Force!
Nu-Sen Flare!
Kai!
Yes!
End of the Sendokai!
Congratulations.
No one had ever beaten
the Grubers before!
Now we can go to the movies, right?
Yes, I just have to drop
Ona off at home before-
Dad! Mom!
There goes my movie.
You have to be very brave
to master that beast.
It has earned the
respect of the Grubers
You, follow me.
We're here.
We're here too
watching TV.
It's not like we went out
and just got back.
Oh, no, not at all.
Are you watching TV
with the TV off?
There's nothing good on.
I like it better this way.
Zak!