[Music]
ah
[Applause]
[Music] [
Music] [
Music]
hello with Miss Chloe, please, yes, yes, she
called me to make you an offer. Would you like to go to the
movies this afternoon
with a certain gentleman, well, of course
I  I am very interested in this offer
accepted yes perfect
Mr. Faa who will be at the cinema at
4 great but the gentleman would say
that this one should not be forgotten I know very well
but for whom I put it clearer that I am not
going to forget you better I don't like it
ending up at the door of the cinema for
three quarters of an hour I can't
believe it
[Music]
milan
chloe what are you doing here I came from buying
some records and you went to the cinema alone
well I came for an offer you
know how those sellers are they
always lie
and  it is arranged in the b you know them they
love it is the red album says it is the
best well I was going home to listen to it
now I don't know if you want to come
a quiet dance total I have the afternoon
leaders
[Music]
when we have discovered that more now
is the earth  in the past because it has gone
without means there that is the dark genesis
the affairs of the multiverse are no longer my
affairs either now I am a simple
scribe do not act as if it were not
with you if it were not for you this
would not be happening
okay I will tell you  but only if you
defeat me in a local fight
[Music]
be careful when the wind followed
the turnstiles it became very strong
calm down I also learned some
tricks in the vortex let's go so much
it will do no good to delay your defeat more
disguised as a cute but keep going  being
an arrogant brother the fight will
be decided by a single fall
and I
[Music]
more [
Music]
again I am going to grow up
and your parents are not there my father spends
the day outside and my mother well my mother I have
n't seen her for years
and  They don't get along very well, I'm sorry,
calm down, it was worse when they were together
[Music]
walking
are all the art and music books in
life, sometimes it's not what we would like,
but these books are always great, I
don't know what I would do without them,
I know what you mean.
You also play the piano
well before I even composed my songs
in 6
you can play something that they composed and I have
said it for centuries since I play do
n't act modest with Kim no please
leave it let's just go for one song
right and
why do we listen to the album yes  came
[Music]
what are you trying to prove story I'm not
a short this has nothing to do with
sandro shorts
[Music]
of life when poverty exploded I
think I am
[Music] you
should have left me there you
know  what it's like to always live in the
shadow of your sister
- the wise man
everyone admired each other but I already admired you
I admired you
[Music]
and all
in fact horrible things no one is going to
forgive me
e [
Music]
hello zac you meet  Well, I have
been helping my father paint the
garage door and well, the cat
got the paint in and then it came out all over my
face and I forgot what was left.
It's clear that it hasn't been out for
a long time. Ok, thank you,
Chloe.
or not it
happened very well and by the way this is
for you I ca
n't of
course I would really be very excited thank you
but this way you won't get rid of showing me your
songs or dreams
[Laughs]
dark genesis
dark genesis is the origin of the
sun empire  It was en masse millions of years ago the
Thorne empire was born on earth,
according to past legend, it was plunged into
chaos until a leader emerged capable
of uniting all its peoples.
The great yes first united them and then
enslaved them, then without boyfriends or
old wolpo.  just to join the ferret,
that gang is not there, he does not want to
follow anyone's orders, if he has
traveled to the past, it is because if not, God
wants to become the big show,
the fate of the multiverse is
once again in the hands of the boys and not
gods a manipulator makes
people distrust each other the
warriors will have to be a
very strong team fortunately my boys
are a team and breakable
[Music] [
Music]
i [
Applause]
and [
Music]
and
[Music]
[Applause]
[  Music]