[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] [
Music] [
Applause] [
Music]
all my life I have been a subject of the
state always on my knees
[Applause]
but when they turn me into a great hour it
will be the others who  kneel
before me we will provoke the dark genesis and
very soon you will be the great tsar but first it
must be even stronger and I suppose that is why
we are here where if
you will find more energy than in the city
of believers
[Music] it
is strength that already dominates  duos in an
attacking power and the world duos in a defensive power
but we still need to awaken a power of
agility
the lightning
you are the ideal warrior for it
and you should be accompanied by the warrior with
whom you are most connected who it is it is
clear I think we have  a special chemistry
I suppose they are
good we will fight a fight so you can
learn to master the lightning duos in
cool and against whom this time you are going to bring
hamsters with tanks I
will not fight against me
etc
[Music]
ah [
Music]
now it's about I still ca
n't get used to it  to these things
calm happens to all beginners
who start
-being cal
[Music]
fast that here [
Music]
thank you
[Music] [Music
] [
Music]
newbie
[Music]
like how you have done it it is very powerful  It did
n't come out like that when you did the
force
with zac your energy came together you have already
acquired your knowledge
[Music]
years for a network team years
flower we have to release the lightning your
voice
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
that has  failed we are not as
close as we thought we
had not chosen me
ah
[Music]
you want to see how the real shot is done
fly has stung looking at a shot from behind
[Music]
whenever
[Music] you
have covered yourself in glory
[Music]
[  Music]
how about we try to wake up the
sweet lightning but it's the only way
to win is in tokai
it's okay
[Music]
or not [
Music] [
Music]
[Music]
but no
yes
and brand never valued god the queen of
vegetables potatoes
[Music]
I mean I have chalk how is it
something terrible is happening
and
if not god has attacked the city believe he has
absorbed too much energy without it and
he
this does not look good
if something happens to him  bad how will we stop
like this god calm down at least we have
awakened all the powers if you have
awakened mine hey the powers
belong to those who know how to use them I know what
you are doing you have taken away my shot
stop you have taken away the lightning your voice
in and  now you want to take me away
[Music] I
encouraged you to die
no if we can prevent it we have to
find said mobius now and destroy the
box that is this we are going to give
this leech what he deserves
but stay here with danny ma
the others follow me
[Music]
[  Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
I
still do not
remember the words written in the
dark genesis to be the great sun it is not
enough to have an army and be strong
you have to be a leader and a leader
needs a people who follow him
unconditionally and  How am I going to
achieve that like the great tsar achieved
by being the winner of the first great sendai tournament
ah
i
[Music]