and ah
yes ah it
seems to us that he is here he is a little
strange lately it is normal for him to be
upset he could die he just wants to
attract attention you already saw what happened
in the fight because of his damn
desire for prominence
come on we can't let him without reason
escape
after what we humans have done to the
believers in coming for
us if we want our plan to
follow its course we have to hit them
where it hurts the most I'm talking about something
much worse
talk about dividing them
and remember not to hurt them
especially  attack
have been divided into two groups I ca
n't tell which one you are in without means
and now what do we do we have to
separate and what will we do when
we find without reason if we are not
all there it is too risky place you
are right tag because it is the plan of the
future and it is the  we are going to continue
chloe quiet defense and there long to
be behind he took his orders and elbow
and
we are more lost than even in a
discotheque they can't walk very far there
vision
d little
plants
like god is not here
we have to separate him from the yankees be
careful
We can't jump over there it's too
dangerous
more pain
and magnitude than j
celina gets closer better
here we'll lose it
70 you
should hit it harder I know what I'm
doing long of course not even what you say
where is the box of that extra it's not
worth it to me  tell it
or we will hand you over to the other people I'm
sure they will be delighted to see you
too more now he knows who I am
and you say that this was the rhythm God
who has us 3 for dead I already believe it I'm
sure it was the blogs more now
it's  full of undesirables, the inhabitants
of this planet are so stupid that they
accuse each other of the Yaqui plague, do
n't look at me like that, it's not my fault that
it happened, there's no life, someone who knows what's
right, someone like him,
someone who endangers the world.  life of
his team he is not a good leader he had to
catch him he could have become
a jackie that is what you would have
liked right so you could be the
hacker and this
you plan to leave like this podium just don't change
the subject
I went back to chloe and here I go back to  home the
other day
it's your girlfriend
not exactly so why the hell they
have been a very pleasant visit but I
have to go a totally mold you
want to know where it is in the disaster box
to survive
and now
I am the
strong answer when you are alone
and believe me you are  very sober
ah
haha
if they don't talk
god what happened without means he
escaped
you had a lot of fun although I still don't
understand the whole game the sticks
we need them safe and sound for the moment
I hope they do something very important
for us they will do it thanks to them
will call the first big tournament
they want to play and then there will be
the big draw
yes