How did it go?
Sidmodius escaped
We have to find another way
to save you.
Forget about me.
The mission comes first.
I don't care about the mission.
I'm not going to let you die.
There must be something we can do.
Maybe there's one last option
You must go to the Nero-Rock Volcano
And find the Fire Lords.
The Fire Lords?
They are the most powerful beings in
Masara and they guard the Nero Rocks.
Rocks with the power to save lives
Quick, guys.
Priestess.
Why didn't you tell them the truth?
I told them what they needed to know.
Damn Sidmodius!
Always wanted to be the Great Sun.
And he'll do anything to get it.
Not if we stop him.
There's something I don't understand.
Why is Chronam-Yatt helping him?
What does she want?
Even I don't know why
she's helping Sidmodius
Chronam-Sunn!
My sister obeys
forces beyond your understanding.
Evil forces.
We have to go to Masara
and warn the Sen-Kuns!
Only they can stop Sidmodius!
"Masara" is Earth in the past. How
are we going to travel through time?
I'll take you there.
The Nero Rock volcano.
We're in a world with spaceships
and no one invents an elevator.
This is no time for laughing!
We have to get back to
Danima as soon as possible!
Danima wouldn't be in danger if you
hadn't let Sidmodius get away!
You could have stopped him too.
If you keep fighting like little children,
we won't be able to save Danima!
Calm down, Zak Everything
will be fine. You'll see.
I hope so.
Hey, Chloe.
I was thinking...
Yes?
I know I messed up last time,
but.
Do you want to go to
the movies on Saturday?
Wow, I'd love to.
But I already made plans with
Lon to go to a concert that day.
A band we really like is playing.
Ah. Great.
Zak...
Hey guys!
Look!
Wow, what crappy statues.
Looks like the sculptor was in a hurry.
My name is Magmus The Fire Lord
And that's Obsedia
Sorry
I meant the little ones.
They're Lethos and Tectos
Okay, forget me.
What brings you here?
We're looking for a Nero Rock.
Owning a rock
is a big responsibility.
We'll only give it to you if
you beat us in a Sendokai!
Okay.
Let's fight!
Guys we have to give
it our all from the start!
It's all up to us.
Let the Sendokai begin!
Nu-Sen Flare!
Cloe!
Zet-Sen Shot!
No.
Sho-Sen Fire!
Duo-Sen Force!
They're unbeatable.
Zak
We need to use the Duo-Sen Force!
That's impossible.
Lon and I don't get along.
And that's why you're
going to let Danima die?
Out of pride?
You're right
Lon
We have to do it.
For Danima
Duo-Sen....
...Sen!
Nero-Sen Fusion!
We have to stop that.
Duo-Sen Wall!
No!
A Nero Rock
It's yours.
But we lost.
You put aside your
pride to do the right thing.
You deserve it.
Thank you very much.
Danima!
We got the rock!
I knew you would get it!
Nero-At-Sen
Put up your bracelets.
Is that's what I think it is?
Sen-Do-Kai!
These are Nero Armors
Your powers will increase by one level
and you will be able to unleash a new power
Which power is it?
When you are all completely attuned,
you can perform the Nero-Sen Fusion.
That's what the Fire Lords used!
Danima, I don't understand!
How are these suits of armor
going to save your life?
Thanks to it, you will defeat
Sidmodius and save many lives.
But not mine.
What?
Relax
My Sen will return to Masara
In some way, I will
always be with you.
Zak
Carrying this map
is a big responsibility.
It means you'll do
what's best for your team.
Even if it's not what's best for you.
That's your real mission.
Because that's what a Hakuru does.
But I don't know how to do that.
No one does.
Until he learns.
Danima!
Masara has lost its priestess.
Uncertain times are ahead.