yes
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] [
Music] [
Music]
no
[Music] it's
where your sister is, I asked you
to keep an eye on her, just a moment if you have done it [
Applause]
[Music]
lesson
hello
[Music] don't
worry, it was just a scare. I can
tell what you were thinking about
when you were taking care of your sister. You can't
keep your mind elsewhere. I
'm sorry. [Music] [Applause] [Music] well, we've arrived
[Music]
[Applause]  ]
and what is happening in the
mass towns they accuse each other of the Yaquis
and the orchard and it encourages you to become
first vice president of that niang plate and you
have always loved our lands,
don't be stupid, the others have also attacked us
hate  There are 6 Chinese meetings. We
already told you that all this is the fault of
their boyfriends and I told you that I do not know
God in any sign, but since
you arrived and you have not stopped
having terrible misfortunes,
but if you don't have legs
we will enlighten you.  loud and our eyes sting,
these kids can't be the culprits,
I say it was the TVs, they are not
authentic massa flats to listen to, we have been
here for centuries, we are as Marianas
as you, for me you are invaders and
invasions are responded to with claws
[Applause]
[  Music]
everything is going as we planned, let's take
action. Don't be impatient.
We have won thanks to you
[Music]
for the extra inhabitants, being
street is the most important thing we always
resolve our conflicts in the
field
[Applause]
as long as you continue fighting among yourselves
you will be an easy target
you need a leader someone you
trust JCE as a soul
someone who osuna to defeat the
Yaquis and I would be a good leader
you I am the best leader a stone
[Music]
[Applause]
the most area we always resolve
our differences with each other that no
because we held a great tournament in
tokai  and that the winner be your leader
[Music]
is right as new people I propose that the
heads of the towns meet to
decide
the street
[Music] I do
n't like this maybe the tournament thing
wasn't a good idea of ​​course it would be if I
hadn't intervened  This would have ended
very badly
[Music]
since
the leaders of the towns have
defined the following rules
[Music]
anyone will be able to participate in the great
tournament whether they were born en masse
or not
while there is a period of mourning no one
will be able to fight
at the request of  the chronics, any
warrior may be replaced by a
representative that he chooses
and lastly and most importantly, whoever
wins the tournament will be recognized by all the
towns as the new leader.
He will do very well
[Music]
hundred tournament
[Applause] are
presented  To the big tournament we northerners
presented ourselves
iztúris
[Music]
but who didn't
for very little stasiak and they are very
dangerous
simó god
[Music]
please
but 16 s podiums the culprit of the
attacks you
don't get where days he just saved us
thank you very much
[Music] you're
confusing me with someone else I'm the
male ruler
Ivan showed me up at the big tournament damn
it was a great idea to call a
big tournament thank you very much
for the queen of Floyd's mustache where I
am I don't remember anything about
the one that was missing  you arrive in time for the
big tournament of the tournament who needs a
presenter
[Music]
guys we have bad news
[Music] we have
been traveling to the past the
history teacher is going to freak out when I tell him
what one is like we have to discover how he
intends to become without hate  the
great form I'm afraid we already know we have just
called a big
sit street tournament it
will be enough for him to win it to take
power it is the worst thing that could happen
thank you very much
so there is only one solution
you will have to win the first big tournament
in both falls  the story I
'm going to sign up for us
poverty that happens first the law or a
little acting as jakub then he let
himself escape god
the courses are not going much better at
home and now it was he who
caused the big tournament
by the way the registrations are not  they do
there
and their slider
there is a note
dear friends everything has been my fault it
deserves a better calculation that's
why I have decided to leave the team
and not return home I will
never forget you
[Music]
ah