Look at you!
You look handsome.
Hey. Are you laughing at me?
After all the trouble I've
caused, I guess I deserve it.
Duo-Sen Lightning Bolt!
Zet Sen Shot
Damn it!
He could have made you a Yaki!
You would've liked that, right?
It could be you, the
Hakuru, and closer to Chloe.
Why the hell would I do that?
I'm Sestrad's Chest!
You're very alone
Sidmodius got away
I've failed everyone who trusted me.
But you can't blame me for anything.
Come with me if you want,
but with your mouth shut.
I heard that
I can't wait for the tournament.
I can't wait to see their faces
when I come in with my Yakis!
The Yakis won't be
going to the tournament.
What?
Remember what happened every
time the Senkuns have faced them.
Tai-Sen Trail!
Zet-Sen Shot!
Yes!
Damn humans.
You mustn't hate them.
Thanks to them the Great Sendokai
Tournament has been called for today.
Now you just have to win
the great tournament.
Gain the trust of the Masarians
Wait until they are eating
out of the palm of your hand.
And then you'll become the Great Zorn
A new beginning for a new empire.
And what will happen to the Yakis?
For now, they'll stay here.
I have other plans for them.
Sidmodius and Chronam-Yatt
used us to carry out their plan
Sidmodius and the Senkuns
haven't traveled to another dimension.
They've traveled through time!
Exactly.
Masara is Earth, in the past.
According to a legend,
Masara was plunged into chaos
until a leader emerged
capable of uniting all its people
The Great Zorn
Sidmodius time-travelled because he wants to become The Great Zorn
There is only one way to stop Sidmodius;
Destroy Sestrad's Chest
By winning the grand tournament.
If we fail, Sidmodius will
become the Great Zorn
What if we let Sidmodius win?
It can't be worse than the Marshal.
We'll never make it.
Hey, don't talk like that.
Think of all the battles we've
won and the powers we've gained.
Ignis Armor are yours.
Duo-Sen Force
Yeah!
Duo-Sen Wall
Duo-Sen Lightning Bolt
And now we have Nero Armor
You'll see
when we unleash the Nero-Sen Fusion
Nero-At-Sen
Sen-Do-Kai!
It's Nero armor.
We can win, and we will win.
We are still four Sendokai warriors!
We are strong,
fast
and very clever
Yes
That's true.
But we lost our Hakuru
Forget about the one who abandoned you!
I can be your Hakuru!
Then say no more. We
have a tournament to win!
Yeah!
Did you notice that?
Yes. There's something
strange about that kid's energy.
We have to find Zack.
Stupid Sendokai!
Only brings me problems
Ah, look.
You've found a friend.
He reminds me of someone.
We could go to the movies together.
Cool.
What you said about going to the movies...
Is that still on?
What were you saying?
Nothing, forget it
Hey, this is no time for laughing.
I really enjoyed that
Me too
By the way, this is for you.
Forget her We have each
other. We don't need anyone else.