Well, we're here!
This is where the great
Sendokai tournament will be held
The Shohanan Stadium
Lalith!
You're here?
I heard that someone was going to
kick Sidmodius' butt
and I wanted to see it for myself.
Where are Tampo and Kento?
They had business to attend to.
Citizens of Manara!
Masara
Sorry, I just got here.
Citizens of Masara!
Welcome to the first great Sendokai tournament!
Yeah!
At first base, facing the pitcher.
They're all girls.
This is going to be a piece of cake.
I like the style of those girls.
Yeah, they're strong, but...
Let's see who's best
with a do on their feet.
Cloe!
You seem distracted.
Thinking up a tactic
for combat?
Yes, is it that obvious?
You know what?
Maybe it's not
so bad living like this.
Wandering like a wolf.
Hunting like a lion.
Smelling like a skunk.
Yes, I've noticed that too.
What
Kido!
What are you doing here?
Looking for my brothers.
And what are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be with your team?
I don't have a team anymore.
Yakis!
Keenan!
Kiway!
Let the Sendokai begin!
Wow! The Nero armor has made us more powerful!
If he could save us.
He can fight in a tournament.
Neither can we!
I said you had
a chance.
Although we'll still need
another warrior in case
someone gets injured.
Me?
Impossible!
I'm no longer a
warrior, Sendokai.
You're wrong, Za.
But Sendokai is for
life.
It's over, guys.
Things have changed.
But you can't stay
stuck in the past.
Because here and now,
you still have a team.
Who can you trust?
We've been saved.
You have to get back to
participating in the big picture.
We won't be able to stop
Sid Modius.
I've left the Sendokai and...
I have new friends.
That?
Is that a coconut?
Your real friends are
fighting to save the world.
You don't understand.
I've endangered
the people I love.
I let Sid Modius
get away with it.
And because of me...
Danima is dead!
I've done horrible things.
No one will forgive me.
But-
I said no!
He's a coward!
He's like a monster!
I enslaved
entire dimensions.
And yet, the people
who really
cared forgave me.
You know your friends
will forgive you.
But that's not what you fear.
Right?
You blame yourself for
Danima's death.
But she's not
here to forgive you.
And you have to live with that.
I just wanted to be
a good Hakuro.
What did you say?
That I just want to
be a good Hakuro.
Do you really want to
be a good Hakuro?
In that case...
Accept the pain
and fight again!
Just as Danima would have wanted.
Because that's what...
You have to be
really brave.
And it rings a bell.
Anyway.
Damn, he's really strong
We are Masara's only
hope.
I'm afraid you're mistaken
Actually, there's another one
Attention, please!