Zack!
What a joy it is to see you!
You gave us quite the scare, buddy!
You look more painted than
when my mother has a date
You look... changed
That's because I have changed
I'm glad you're back, but
the team is already signed up
I'm afraid you won't
be able to fight with us
I know
But I'll fight with the Kiwuns
Look who's here
Start packing your suitcases, Kiwuns
When we win the fight you will go home
Yeah! And when we win the
tournament you will go to another planet
Damn Norkingos! We're going to-
Unintelligable speech by Keenan, with the Do still stuck in his mouth
Well said, brother
In this fight, the Norkingos and
the Kiwuns will face each other!
I'm going to talk to Zack
That boy needs to hear
a voice with experience
Kento, the enemy of advice will have a
Will he have a disciple
I am not an enemy of advice
It's just that yours are very bad
Let's see which team defeats Sidmodius
Let the Sendokai begin!
Mine!
Let's go Kiwuns!
The Kiwuns take the lead
Kido! Don't Stop!
Stand up to him!
The Kiwuns have nothing
against the Norkingo fury!
Hey!
Why don't you pick on
someone your own size?
Yes! Uh..
Or two half your size!
Keenan! Keeway!
Let's show them what we've got!
Oh no!
The Kiwuns are not made for melee
No-Sen Hammer!
Kai for the Norkingos!
That Baron Ragnaki is very powerful
I can feel his energy
Can we beat him?
I think so
But that woman... There
is something evil about her
We need other teams to
be able to stand up to him.
Zack!
The Kiwuns cannot face
others in hand-to-hand combat
You have to change your way of thinking
A good leader not only knows
his strengths and weaknesses
He also knows those of his team
The Kiwuns are not strong,
but they are agile and elusive
Hey guys!
Change of strategy
Avoid contact! Make
them run and tire them out!
Stop whispering and fight like men!
No, not like men! We
will fight like Kiwuns!
Yay!
The Kiwons have reacted!
Kai for the Kiwuns!
for you
The combat is very even!
Yes!
Yeah!
This is not going to end like this!
The Norkingos counter attack!
They haven't said the last word yet
Let's go!
We can't get through it!
No!
Kai for the Norkingos!
Damn it
We won't be able to take
down this shield with just speed
Zack! The Kiwuns have
been students of Danima
We can also use Duo-Sen powers!
Keenan, Keeway. Protect the
Senrock with the Duo-Sen Wall
Kido, you're with me
Haven't you had enough yet?
The Norkingos attack with all their might
This move could be final!
No-Sen Hammer!
Duo-Sen Wall!
Kido! Yours!
No-Sen Shield
Duo-Sen Force!
Incredible!
Double-Kai for the Kiwuns!
Letting them Win the Sendokai
No.
Yeah!
This deserves a Conga-Tongue
Congratulations, guys. What a fight!
Thank you
Do you guys realize?
Now we have two teams
that can beat Sidmodius!
But the only way to defeat
Sidmodius is with the Nero-Sen fusion
And only we can only do that
We can kick his ass
just as much as you guys!
No, Keenan. He's right
We only have one Nero Armor
That has a solution....
A Nero Rock!
Sendokai!
This armor will increase your power
Remember that releasing the nero-sen
fusion depends on your rapport as a team
This means you need to find a common goal
Something only a good Hakuru can achieve
Damn Magmus
Now two teams are conspiring to defeat me
You don't have to worry. Before they
get to you, they'll have to face each other
And the Kiwuns move on to the next phase!
Along with the Kevvers and the Humans!
A new and powerful force
will be decisive in this battle....
Jealousy.