Bravo. You've become
a very dangerous warrior
But remember
Winning the tournament
isn't enough to take control
You have to win over the audience
Win over the audience?
First, you must show yourself vulnerable
Pretend that you are in danger
The audience will sympathize with you
And when they think that all is lost
We will give an unexpected twist
to the situation with a final surprise.
They will not see you as a warrior,
But as a hero
A hero?
I like it
Kiet!
Get up! I need you to help
me move a piece of furniture
Five more minutes
No!
It has to be done now
I'm tired
I haven't seen you this tired in a while!
More or less...
Since you fought those monsters
Like the last time
It's very important that no one on
earth knows about the big tournament
It could cause panic
Moving furniture? I
love moving furniture!
Do you want me to take
the wardrobe up to the roof?
This Sendokai thing is going to finish me!
Fenzi, darling!
I'm going to get a massage with rose petal oils
and I was wondering if you'd like to join,
you know, a girls' afternoon, a massage
A massage?
Maybe it would be good for me.
Okay!
It's not like you to want
a rose petal massage
Is something wrong?
Uh, no. It's just that
I'm really into the whole
cheesy stuff now
And flowery things, like
strawberry-scented stuff
I love it!
What joy, my daughter. You'll see what a
great afternoon we're going to have together!
Chloe, are you okay?
Yeah
Well, I'm confused about
a problem....
A homework problem!
Oh, I can help you with that!
So, explain that problem to me
Well, there's a train that
leaves a city at 115km/h
And the train can go to two cities
A very interesting and
sensitive boy lives in one city
And in the other there
lives a very funny boy
who is a bit of a mess, but the
kindest in the whole universe
I see
The question is: Which
path should the train choose?
I suppose at some point in the journey,
the driver will know where they want to go.
They just have to follow their feelings
I don't know what the
passengers will think of this system
If the heart chooses the
destination, believe me
There will be no better trip
Dad?
Lon?
Remember that group of friends I found?
Well, they've named me leader of the gang.
Now I'm a boss like you!
It's easy being named a leader
The hard part is staying
Thanks to me, my company
is a leader on five continents
But I'm surrounded by a bunch of
hyenas who want to steal my place!
I am going to my room
Be careful, Lon
Your true enemies are not your adversaries,
but those who are by your side.
They will want to take away what is yours.
We're here! Did you remember
to give your sister dinner?
Yes, I did.
Very good. Well, now we just have
to pick up her toys from the living room
I've done that too.
Wow! You've become quite
responsible all of a sudden.
Are you okay?
You're not saving the world again, are you?
No, don't worry about that.
Good night!
We have the winners of the first phase.
Yes!
So, as the master of ceremonies
I'm putting on the second phase
of the Great Sendokai Tournament!
Great!
Open the floodgates
The map!
How weird
What's going on?
Silence, please.
In today's Sendokai, The Baron
Ragnaki and Nasto will face off!
Why are they "boo"ing him?
Nasto feeds on the Masarian's crops
They devastate the fields and cause famines
If Nasto wins the Grand
Tournament, we will have a problem
It's not going to end well either way
Let the Sendokai begin!
The Baron takes the do and
runs towards the Senrock!
But Nasto doesn't react!
Move, slug!
By Flor's drool! Nasto's
releasing a lot of insects!
Damn it!
Kai for Nasto!
Out!
The Baron fights back!
Kai for the Baron Ragnaki!
He's pretending!
He's not like that!
It seems that Nasto is
not going to be crossed.
My mother!
He just released a giant insect.
My son! Where is my son!
A child has just fallen into the field
My son!
Oh no! The insect is heading towards him!
We have to save him
The Baron Ragnaki just saved the child!
Unbelievable!
He's crossing the field with a child
Sid-Sen Energy!
Double-Kai!
It's the end of the fight!
Damn manipulator
The Baron Ragnaki has not only won
But has heroically saved a child's life!
Thank you very much baron
Ragnaki!
a hero
has become a bad hero.