Guys, I got it!
Magnus said that to
activate the Nero-Sen Fusion
We had to find a common goal, right?
Well, our goal is to defeat
Sidmodius! So let's think about him.
Nero-Sen Fusion!
Nothing
It's not working
Guys, this whole "exploding
every five minutes" isn't cool
Yeah. Finding a common
goal is very difficult
I don't know if I'll
be able to do it
Relax, we just need to rest
Rest?
That I know how to do.
I'm the Hakuru of resting.
I also envied my brother
for thousands of years
I know you'd like to be with them
Be their Hakuru
But if you really care about
them, it's best to stay away.
I'm here!
Whose suitcase is this? Mom's?
They're mine.
I'm leaving
The company is doing very badly in the East
I have to go and take care of it personally
What?
How long will you be gone?
I don't know
But I'll deposit money for
you. You won't miss anything.
I don't care about the damn money
You can't buy me like one of your lackeys!
I won't allow you to speak to me like that.
You're abandoning me like
mom did! You're worse than her!
Lon!
Are you okay? If you need to
talk, you know you can trust me
Yeah, I'm fine
In the next Sendokai match,
The Human Team will face Lesay
Lesay?
He really exists!
Who is he?
A wizard
In Masara, the mothers tell their children
that if they don't behave well,
Lesay will come and give them nightmares
That guy gives me the chills
Let the Sendokai begin!
I got it!
The Humans take the do!
They're approaching the Senrok! And....
Kai!
Lesay hasn't even lifted a finger!
I think that under that mask he's asleep
Lesay and just released some kind of fog.
What is this I don't feel well...
What's going on?
That fog is using their
fears to cause hallucinations.
The Humans are behaving strangely
Cloe!
Zak!
Lon!
Come with me
Damn Selfish!
Who do you think pays for this house?
Dad?
I wish we never met!
I've thrown my life away!
I hate you!
Mom!
No! Please don't fight again!
Not again!
Kai for Lesay!
Come on guys, react!
Those visions aren't real.
It's your mind deceiving you.
Oh, not by all the gods of the Sen!
What's wrong?
I just remembered where I know
her from. That woman is Chronam-Yatt!
Come with me.
Cloe, you have to choose one of us
Of course!
If the mind deceives you, then...
Guys! Don't believe what
you see, follow your heart!
If the heart chooses the destination,
believe me, there will be no better journey
A Human has managed to break free!
Ignore the visions! Let
your heart guide you!
Let your heart guide you!
And what about me?
Unintelligible Arguing
Look what you did!
Your mother is leaving
And it's your fault!
No!
It wasn't my fault!
We don't want you
No one loves you!
You're alone.
Kai for Lesay!
One more and the victory will be his!
Oh no!
We need to protect the Senrok!
Lon!
We need you!
I'm alone
Lon
You're not alone
You're not alone!
I'm here with you
Cloe
You just won a fight. But
we still have another one.
Duo-Sen Lightning Bolt!
The Humans react!
They're approaching the Senrok!
Kai for the Humans!
They won the Sendokai!
Yeah!
Cloe
I wanted to thank you
for what you did today.
It was very important to me.
Ah, no need
Congratulations!
You really are the best
Hakuro they can have
Thank you. With this
team. Nothing can go wrong.
I wouldn't be so sure....
The woman accompanying
Sidmodius is not a simple Chron.
She and her sister were
created by the gods of Sen
To maintain the balance of
good and evil in the Multi-Verse
Chronam-Yatt is a goddess of evil.
That is absurd!
Absurd... But true
By defeating the Zorn empire you
tilted the balance and good triumphed.
Now, my sister wants to
return the multiverse to darkness
And Sidmodius is her puppet
She may have Sidmodius,
But we have.... each other!
Yeah!
Well said!