Guys! To activate the Nero-Sen Fusion
We must find a common goal
But what can the Kiwuns
and I have in common?
I got it, the burps.
Are you sure about that?
Everyone likes burps!
Alright, we can try it
Nero-Sen Fusion
It's going to be hard to master the fusion.
Don't worry, we still have a secret weapon!
The Kido-Sen Attack!
What the heck?!
Too bad we're not in a spitting tournament
We would surely win
Do you really intend on
activating the Nero-Sen Fusion?
Only the masters of fire have achieved it
And you are nothing more than...
Slimy peasants
We are not peasants, nor are we slimey-
We are not peasants!
Whatever you say....
Those Credlers have been treating
us like bumpkins for centuries.
Oops.. Sorry
I'll be right back
Hey, Chloe!
Zack!
How's it going?
You've got a match coming up, no?
Yeah
I hope I'm not late
Don't worry. You've never been late, Zack
Zack!
Ready for the fight.
Always
If you win, we'll face
each other in the next one.
Yes, I suppose so
Attention, please! Team Credler
and team Kiwun, come to the field!
They're calling me. See
you in the next match!
I hope they do well.
Well, I don't.
Anyone who's not on our team is our rival,
and it's best not to hang out with rivals.
but
[Music]
the more they do the street
[Applause]
[Music] it
is their oven that flies, these
peasants say, like you,
to hell with the chickens
[Music  ]
boys
[Music]
[Applause]
those grown-ups are the best only
because they are smarter, richer, more
beautiful and stronger but we are
more
[Applause]
no,
those fools are full of resentment or they are
not going to achieve anything  they cannot
[Music]
lohan to release a joint power
[Applause]
according to todd stern [
Applause]
come on our difficult is like a field
of yours but without vegetables
[Music]
[Applause]
do not let the emotions  dominate us,
control our anger and you will have
control of the fight,
guys, don't waste your energy
hating them, ferrat their mouths and respond to
their insults with your feet by kicking I don't
allow that
no
[Applause] [
Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
[Applause  ]
about putting on those insect eaters,
our comments don't seem to affect them, there
's no point in enjoying those who don't get
offended, we'll do the same thing that they keep silent about,
and in fighting
[Music]
[Applause]
the teams have totally changed
for now on the list,
let's do it  the sweet door
[Music]
[Applause]
then I
have to protect it
[Music]
when the level or the pure
I take care of it
[Music] [
Music] they
are too strong to remain more
secret [
Applause]
[Applause]
[Music]
and
[Applause]
[Music] we
have come to congratulate you
and to thank you. It has been many
centuries since we have enjoyed the holy chalice so much
after what you did to us in the
past because one day
they came and said that as  You guys who
did
something, we've been watching the ones
that arrive for so long and we remember the reason,
it's true,
oh,
and better
look what we've managed to
make us become friends with the bears 0 2 [
Laughs]
congratulations, you won thanks to the fact that it's
good for your parents, yes, no.  Let's be in
a spitting tournament
hey, I was thinking, we have
an afternoon at the movies pending,
Chloe, there's a lot at stake in this tournament,
we can't let our emotions
dominate us, and it seems like things
are going well for you with the con,
no, I don't even think so.  It would be better if we do
n't talk again until all this is
over
I guess you're right from
now on we are rivals
friends rivals
[Music]
ah