It would be better if we didn't talk until this is all over
Ugh. But- But what's it about
Although he has a point
The tournament comes first
No!
It's more important to act like someone with feelings!
What if it's an excuse?
What if he doesn't like me anymore?
Ugh, what a mess
This can't possibly get more complicated
Lon! What's up?
Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you
I wanted to talk to you,
Talk... About what?
You see, the other day in the fight I realized something
I-
I like you it's Chloe.  I like you a lot.
And, well. I was wondering if you feel the same
Lon-
Hey, don't worry.
It's no big deal
But it's still important to me
We're friends, right?
Yeah
If not, who's going to give you records?
That's true
If Fenzy loans me her heavy metal albums,
my head might explode
It's because of Zack, right?
You like him
What? No no no it's not that!
In the next battle,
the Baron Ragnaki and the fire masters will face each other!
There is no Baron Ragnaki.
You can't deceive, we know the truth
The truth?
The truth is whatever the inhabitants of Masara believe
And Masara believes me.
Masara-Sendo-Kayetsu
Let the Sendokai begin!
What a move!
The Masters of Fire are heading to the Senrock!
Kai!
Yeah!!
Yeah!
The Baron Ragnaki reacts!
Running with the do
But he loses it!
The rivals are clearly superior!
The audience can't help you win
They wont, but the energy I stole will
What's this?
Oh no!
He's going to use all the energy he has in Sestrad's chest!
The Baron has transformed!
Now he's stronger and- Wow!
He certainly has some fine abs
Incredible!
Kai to the Baron Ragnaki!
Conceited.
You're nothing more than stones, and you fight as such
Second Kai to the Baron Ragnaki!
One more and he takes this victory!
You asked for it. You leave us no other choice
The masters of fire are about to unleash some kind of....
Force!
Nero-Sen-
There it is....
Fusion!
It looks like the Fire Masters are going to win the
fight with this Kai!
The Baron saves this situation at the last possible moment
now come back
of course where are you going in such a hurry
no god is too strong let's go we have to
use the function again yes
I want to talk to tag that won't be
possible  I understand what you feel but
you can't let emotions
interfere with your mission if it
really matters' fac it's better if we don't
see each other until this is all over
in which case could you give her this from me I'm
sorry Chloe this is not the time for this
[  Music]
that I knew
and they knew
[Music]
hidden with us but it would happen to us they will
end up unmasking us it can
happen to you these are the most powerful beings
of clarity the eyes play with their fragile
in their stories that they have done to
stop the Yaquis exactly no  just
need someone took well came back
yesterday to god I offer to me he died
[Music]
and again this map has been broken it has
not been broken I am reacting like the
public and this is more than just a simple
kill
or not if not god has won  In that case
you better learn to use
nero sen fusion because you are the last
hope the multiverse calm down if
we don't make it I'm sure I
think the guys will do it as a
team that one more now I don't know
hey guys  Before the
fight begins, I wanted to wish you luck, of course, that
the best team wins. If the kibbutz
lose, release the fusion and give them a
choice, as well as God, on our side,
friends, friends, friends,
rivals, and I confess that I'm going to
feel a little sad kicking the ball.  rear
a question fifth has given something on
my part human type and reason do not go
to the field I
do not know
where they are