Both teams are very even!
May I?
Only if you promise not to complain
And why would I?
You always complain when your team loses
Kido, Yours
That boy is not clean wheat
You are right, Something is not going well
And it could even get worse
Chronan Sun!
Enjoy the show
I'm going to start the
final phase of our plan
Guys! Avoid his attacks like
we did with The Norkingos!
We are more agile
We will not let ourselves
be defeated by some lizards!
What did you just call us?
Calm down, guys. Remember
what happened with the Kredlers.
We have to focus on the combat
and not get carried away by emotions
The Kiwun team is getting
dangerously close to the Human Senrok
But what are you doing?  Stop them!
Zet-sen...
Tai-sen trail!
...Shot!
Kai From the Kiwuns
Yay!
Damn
Yupiii
Yupi?
Leave me alone
We have to activate the Nero-Sen Fusion
But we haven't found a common goal
I'll Give You One. We Have to Hate Zack!
What?!
What do the 4 of us have in
common? That Zack betrayed us!
That's what unites us
Uncle, I don't see it
You're right Lon, I don't think it's...
Enough, it's not time to
argue, but to obey your Hakuru
It seems that the Human team
is preparing to Counterattack!
Nero-Sen fusion
They're going to activate
the Nero-sen fusion!
Us too! Quick, let's think of a common goal
I have it! Gargling with Mucus
Yes!!
Are you sure that...
Very well, let's try it!
Everything is going according to my plans
Spirits without Sensation, The time
has come to fulfill your true mission
You will come with me And we will return
the Multi-verse To the abysses of darkness
I don't know what you intend to do...
Sister...
...But I'm not going to
let you get away with it.
Nero-sen fusion
How could it fail? What's
more cool than gargling mucus?
By the Buttocks of King Trog!
Both teams have tried to unleash a
great power, and they have failed Let's
Try again
No!
We will never feel hate for
Zack, because he is our friend
You will feel what I tell you
Do you prefer a traitor to your own Hakuru?
Well, I'll win the fight ALONE.
Tai-sen trail
I don't understand. It looks like a
human is going to face The Kiwuns alone.
Eh, but how did he do that?
He acquired our powers while
we were doing the Nero-sen fusion
Geo-sen shockwave!
Yao-sen vision!
Zet-sen shot!
Kai for the Human team!
Or at least... one Human
You have started a war that you cannot win
The truth is on our side, We will defeat
Sidmodius
And we will erase Evil from the multiverse
Sidmodius... Do you still
think Sidmodius is the key?
Where is your smile now?
Enough
This is not Sendokai. We are
not going to let you fight like this
Give us the Do
Traitors!
I can't trust anyone!
Lon, give us the Do
No!
Geo-sen shockwave!
Goa-Sen shield
Wow! The Human Just
Immobilized His Own Team!
Oh No, He's Lost His Reason
Lon, Stop!
You are like my father! Like my
mother! And you, Chloe!
You are the worst. You made me believe that
you cared! That I was not alone!
You are not alone, Lon
Lies! Always Lies!
I don't need you! I don't need anyone!
Sidmodius Is a Simple Piece.
There Are Others Who Fight For
Me And They Don't Even Know It
Because Evil Dwells In All Beings
As long as there is someone who suffers,
someone hurt, someone alone.
I will make the Flame of Hate
grow. And I will turn him into My deer
That's why it's impossible to defeat me
And that's why, Sister, Evil will reign again!