We Have to activate the Nero-Sen Fusion
But We Haven't Found a Common Goal
We Have to Hate Zack
We'll Never Hate Zack
Because He's Our Friend
Come With Me And We'll Return The
Multiverse to the Abysses of Darkness
I'm not going to let you get away with this
Sister...
Chloe, You Are the Worst
The Human Warrior Heads Alone
towards the Senrok of His Rivals!
Geo-Sen Shockwave!
Go-sen Tornado!
Kinan!, Kiwey!
My boys!
Nu-Sen Flare!
Kai from the Human Team!
Brothers! Are you okay?
I feel like a Norkingo sat on me
Kido, you'll have to fight for us.
What?  But I...
Oh No!!, Why did Kido's Slob
have to stay? We are doomed!
We are not doomed! And I am not a jerk!!
I am Kido The Destroyer!!!
Caramba!! The Short Kiwun Has
out-played the Human Warrior!!
What do we have here, huh?
Tai-Sen Trail!
Geo-Sen Shockwave!
Kido!!
Wow!! There are only 2
warriors left on the field!!
No, Lon! Why?
This has gone too far.
Evil will once again rule the multiverse
Sister, it's too late to stop it from going
Come along, Yakis! The time has come.
Where are you taking them?
No, stop!
You stop me, if you can
Your effort is useless.
Join me, sister, and we will see
together how the Multiverse burns!
I am not one of your Puppets!
I am the Goddess of Good!
And the Duty of a goddess
of Good is to fight Evil!!
The Combat is Very Even!
Zet-Sen shot!
Zet-Sen Shot!
You couldn't stand that
I was the Hakuru, right?
That's why you stole
the only thing I had left.
What the heck are you talking about?
Chloe!
You feel that?
Feel what?
Loneliness
Everyone Has Fallen. And
Now you're the only one left
That's What My Life Consists
Of, and now yours too!
No, Lon! Please!
Zack!
Sho-Sen Fire!
No!
Kido!
My boy!
By Brott's Gums!!
One of the Kiwuns has sacrificed
himself to protect his teammate!!
Kido!
Kiwey
Kinan
Fools!!
You help each other, but you are alone!
You are alone!
No Lon, You don't understand
Precisely in the darkest hours
It's when you feel the most that
there is someone by your side.
Listen to this and don't forget: A Sendokai
Warrior is never alone if he has a team
That's impossible! How-
Nero-Sen Fusion!
Incredible! When it seemed
impossible, Team Kiwun has won the fight!!
Zack!
Kido!
Zack, are you okay?
I'm alright, don't worry about me.
the Kiwuns have taken the worst part.
Kido...
I think there won't
be any Lenguaconga today
Kido... I... I want to
tell you something... I
haven't always been fair to you,
sometimes I... I don't know how to say
I'm sorry...?
Alright, alright. I forgive you!
No Dad, that's what
you're trying to say!
Ah! Yes it's true! That's it
Kido, you've behaved like a true Warrior!
Poor Naives! Your Joy will not last long!
The Humans are eliminated and
these Kiwuns will take months to recover.
There is only one warrior left
to face me! Good Luck, Zack...
He May Have Become Very
Strong. But He's Still a Vermin!
Still, you're right. The Kiwuns
can't fight, we only have Zack left
...Unless we abide by Kronyan's
Law and you join Team Kiwun!
That is, if you accept
me back into the team...
That's it, It's done dude!
Well of course we accept you!
You've always been Our Hakuru, Zack
The team fights together again...
Together, we will defeat Sidmodius!!!
Yes!
Surrender! I do not want to hurt you!
That's why you and I are so different!!
And That's Why I Win!
You see?  In the end You joined Me
We can't leave Lon Here
Are you serious?!  After what he's done?!
He Needs help. Where is he?
I hate you all!