[Music]
ah
[Applause]
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [
Applause] [
Music]
evil has arrived it will reign again
[Music]
good very good
kingdom don't do it there
is energy in all beings you have to
respect them  A
very wise person taught it to me, his name was Anima, and I wish I
could have saved people.
Now the only thing I can do for them
is to be a good hacker or invent, assigned
to God, look who we have here
[Music]
today you stay in this dimension.
it could be that I'm always lying around
doing nothing there's nothing to please
move fly contains you talk that's the
microwave see you
later well
yes I'm in the microwave where I put
the sheet
[Music]
between the sheets I'm a warrior sendo
cai I don't  I imagine the masters of the fire
doing the laundry I'm
sorry but we can't understand it
[Music]
how strange the weatherman said he
would do son I'm leaving I'm staying
[Music] [
Music]
I'm going to stay giving to the kids
have a good time  true
mom, remember that the problem that I
explained to you about the train, if I was right, the
driver has already chosen his divine destination
[Music]
about 90
i
[Music]
today is the big day we will finally be able to
defeat without hatred but first I want to
tell you that I am very happy  to fight
by your side again I know that as long as we
are together nothing will stop us
and what about long when he disappeared he
was like talking we have to find
him and help him but we can't do it
until the tournament is over and there is another
issue that worries me to win
We will need the fusion but I know how
you managed to free it, the kings, some
milestones and how you found your
common goal. It was strange. I think it
wasn't so much what we shared but how
we shared it, as
if we all wanted the same thing but
each one in their own way,
okay, I do
n't get it.  I think what we shared
was a feeling
so we will have to train
feelings I'm afraid that's not
possible but I'm sure it's something
we'll find as we fight or
so I hope
the moment of truth has arrived
[Music]
beyond that we feel like Bulgarians that maybe
I am a girlfriend along with Estíbaliz, they feel
intimidated and he does not appear
when he is our own leader,
always complete for our enemies, God
depends on the tyrants and the evil ones
[Applause]
but upon arrival, when the countdown ends,
they will be disqualified
[Music]
as he arrives  before you are thinking
we have a feeling in
common because I believe that if I feel something
cloud the truth is that it doesn't matter
now
to release the fusion we need a
feeling that the four of us share
not only you and I agree it
seems we
can't leave now  but if we are not going
to go to the disqualification and if not
bye he will win the big tournament there
is still time
[Music] I
don't like this a space where
the boys are
[Music]
to find the missing one
[  Music] [
Music]
sorry you're disheveled
[Music]
fight the Yankees forget about the
tournament
ah [
Music] I
think face here you
should be winning a tournament
we can't leave you alone respect
young man these geezers know how to
defend themselves
when
brothers fight together again like
in the old days let's see who
knocks down the most and what is it
no
[Music] they do
n't kill me
it is clear that they are not going to show up
well
[Music]
this farce comes to an end sign god the
fury of all those who
a year ago
cain  to survive
[Music]
i