incredible sendokai music
!!!  You
You've always been our hakuro, Zack
Together, WE WILL DEFEAT SIDMODIUS!!!
Yes!!
You see?  You finally joined me.
You should be winning a tournament
Wait!!!!
The fury of all those you have hurt will fall on you today.
The human warriors have arrived just in time.
Hah! Suck that one!!!
Well, without further delay, let's start the final of the Grand Tournament.
It's time...
SENDOKAI!!!!
[Crowd Cheering]
Ragnaki! Ragnaki! Ragnaki! Ragnaki!
Masara-Sendo-Kayetsu
Let the Sendokai begin!
Baron Ragnaki steps forward and takes the Do
Not so fast...
Nu-Sen Flare!
Geo-Sen Shockwave!
Go-Sen Tornado!
Hey?
The 2 teams are very even!!!
How about we stop warming up and start fighting seriously?
Baron Ragnaki has fallen!
It seems as if he has received a blow
CHEATING Humans!!!
But he is pretending!!!
I already know that trick
EH!  He escaped!
Kiet! Fenzy! Go for it!!!
Sid-Sen...
Tai-Sen Trail!
Hey?
The Humans get The Do and prevent a Kai from Baron!
20, 21, and 22, I'm winning
Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, I've beaten 23...
But the little one doesn't count
Stop behaving like children. You look like you are 200 years old!!!
I'll have to make it a little more difficult for them...
What's happening?
Oh, look!
Oh no!
Where did all those monsters come from?!?
How horrible... And Zack is out there!
We can't find our children. By any chance, could they be here?
Oh no... They've done it again...
Look, I told Kiet not to save the world anymore!
We have to go out and fight with them!!!
But if we are nothing more than human,
I refuse to let a pack of monsters take over our planet without fighting back!
Careful Tanpo! Behind you!
Hi handsome... I thought you wouldn't come back...
To the attack!
Sid-Sin...
Duo-Sen Wall!
Sho-Sen Fire!
Sid-Sen Shild!
It seems that the Baron is having a hard time Fighting at the level of Humans
Yoohoo! That's how it's done!
Yes! High five!
Come on, what are you waiting for?
Hmmm... When it comes to Sidmodius, I wouldn't trust too easily
Don't you realize?
These people don't care about you at all! They don't deserve your help, why do you do it?  Why do you fight?
For Masara, for The Earth, and for Danima...
Ahhhh yes... I'm sorry about the old lady.
I shouldn't have stolen so much energy from her when I transformed her into Yaki...
So If he transformed her... That means that...
Exactly! That I absorbed her powers!
Masara - SEN - FRACTAAA!!!
Amazing! Baron Ragnaki has divided himself into 4 warriors!
That's Danima's technique! He stole it, see?!?  That means he turned Danima into Yaki!!!  He is guilty of everything!
Suddenly the forces are equal again!
This is getting difficult
I have to stop Sidmodius
Sid-Sen Ira!
Kai of Baron Ragnaki!
It can't be
This is unheard of! I had never seen a warrior with the Baron's strength