I hate you all!
Someday I will be strong,
and this won't happen again
I will create a more just world.
A world without pain!
The Zorn Fortress!
This is where Zack the traitor
and the others defeated the Zorns!
At last!
Strike!
Remind me not to come
with you on the next invasion
I will do that, if there is a "next time"
Baron Ragnaki's team
has scored their first Kai!
And take possession
He's playing dirty!
Is THIS the leader you want for Masara?
Sidmodius has all of Danima's powers!
We can't stop him!
He may have Danima's powers
But we have something more important!
Her teachings!
Yeah!
Go-Sen Tornado!
The humans have reacted!
Wow! Their rapport is impressive!
Zet-Sen Shot!
Kai for the Humans!
No!
Yes!
See? Clean fighting!
That's how real heros fight!
Humans! Humans! Humans!
Damn traitors. The Baron is
the man you should worship
Huh? The map is feeling
the energy of the public again!
But this time it looks.... different
He's reacting
When Zack finally discovers
the true power of the map
Nothing will stop them.
But only a true Hakuru
can [something] the map
And Zack isn't ready yet
Not until you face your own limits.
Also, there's something
about this fight that I'm not liking
You asked for it....
Oh no....
A nero rock!
He must've stolen it from
me when he fought us
Nero... at... Sen!
Huh?!
The Baron has transformed again!
Quiet! Do not move!
Relax, Lon
I'm not here to hurt you
Do you know who that helmet belonged to?
It belonged to the
founder of the Zorn Empire
He was a warrior with a vision
He didn't stop until he
got everything he wanted
And he wanted the
same thing as you, Lon
Me?
Wouldn't you like to be
stronger and create a new world?
A more just world.
A world without pain.
Whoever wears that
helmet will rule the Multiverse
And will put an end to all
those who made him suffer
Whoever wears that helmet
will become The Great Zorn
Oh no! They're going to
activate the Nero-Sen Fusion!
Kiet! Fenzy!
You have to use
the Duo-Sen Wall!
The wall wont resist the fusion!
I know. But it will
absorb the impact!
Chloe, you're with me!
Duo-Sen Wall!
Nero-Sen Fusion!
Now!
Kai for the Baron Ragnaki!
One more and he will
win the Grand Tournament!
Oh no. If Sidmodius uses the Fusion
on them again, he'll destroy them
It's over. This is the end
It can't be! What
are we going to do?!
We're going to activate
the Nero-Sen fusion!
But we don't know what
feeling we have in common
Since we met, we've been
through so much together
We've been beaten,
ridiculed, shot,
We've suffered
On Earth
And in the depths
of the Multiverse
But we kept moving forward
Maybe one day we won't
be able to save ourselves
But today is not that day.
Because even if we lose
everything, we still have our friendship
And that's what matters
Because that's the
feeling that unites us
Nero-Sen Fusion!
Come on, guys!