Attack!!
Whoever wears that helmet will become
the great Zorn
Masara-Sen-Fracta!
He's split himself into four warriors!
Nero-At-Sen
Nero-Sen Fusion!
It's over
Let's hold on as long as we can. We have to
buy time for your children
to destroy Sestrad's Chest.
After so many years being enemies
We are going to die as companions.
Maybe you are right, but first
we are going to fight as brothers
Attack!
Come on, Lon. Become the Grand Zorn
And everything I said will be fulfilled.
I don't need you to achieve
that! I am a Sendokai Warrior!
I can offer you a lot more
What did you do?
I am a Chron. I can
dominate space and time.
I transmitted my most
valuable power to the helmet
Because others can only
dream to wear the helmet
Whoever wears the
helmet will become immortal
The Baron Ragnaki takes
the majority of the field
Why are you fighting?
My fusion is more powerful than yours!
I've stolen the energy from
thousands of Masarians!
Maybe you can steal energy
But you can't steal our feelings!
How is this possible?
Kai.... For the Humans
The humans win the
grand Sendokai tournament!
My energy!
Give me back my energy!
The chest is damaged
His power over the Yakis is going to fade
The Senkuns did it!
Yes! The gang have defeated Sidmodius!
Chronan-Yatt, where are you?
Damn you!
You've failed, Sidmodius
At last! The people of Masara
are going to know the truth.
Who's this "Sidmodius"?
I'm the Baron Ragnaki!
These have nothing to do with me!
It's him!
He transformed us into Yakis!
We wanted to give you [something]
Thanks to you, the earth is a free planet
No. Congratulations to you!
Now I know where your children's talent
for combat comes from
Please. Sentimentality gives me a headache.
Who?
For me?
Thank you....
Hey! You're the famous Kiet
who saved the multiverse twice!
In the flesh!
And you're legendary Fenzi
Not very tall, but very fast!
Yeah!
The great Sendokai tournament has finished!
And  as everyone agreed
The leader of the winning team
Will be Masara's new leader!
Congratulations, Zack
You wanted to be a good Hakuru
And you've become the
best Hakuru in the multiverse
Thank you. It's a great
honor, but I cannot accept it
It was with the Kiwuns that I learned
the true meaning of being a Hakuru
That is why your leader should be a Kiwun
The noblest and bravest in themselves
Thank you, Thank you! I don't deserve it
Kido.
What?! But I don't know how?
Just like Danima says
Put on the helmet, Lon
Become the Great Zorn
But I'm not evil
This has nothing to do with good and evil
It's about justice
Because only by being
the great Zorn can you
Make justice fall on those
who abandoned you on
Those who lied to you
And made you believe they loved you
Those who betrayed you
and stole what was yours
Like Zack!
Traitor!
Sidmodius....
We had a deal! I was
going to be The Great Zorn!
I always knew Lon would be The Great Zorn
I used for my purposes like a puppet
Look what your puppet is doing!
My mission is complete
Evil has come back
The portal isn't working!
Something has happened to the Cronix
Oh no!
If the portal doesn't work, the team
will be trapped in Masara.... forever
At last, it's all over!
If everything is over, does it mean
we can finally talk about ourselves?
What's that sound?