Sidmodius has lost control over Sestrads Chest
He has become a superior of super yaki
Un oh, He's coming towards us!
Get out of here, quickly!
Chloe! Let's use the Duo-Sen Lightning to snatch the rock out of his hands
Duo-Sen-
Duo-Sen Wall!
Chloe. I think we will only be able to activate the Lightning Bolt once we're honest with each other
Zack!
That's what I've been trying to tell you for a long time
I... I...
I love you
Chloe- I-
Oh no! SidYaki is going to destroy Masara!
That's not going to happen. Come on, guys!
Nero-Sen Fusion!
We can't do it
Run!!!
Zack!
You have the most powerful weapon in Masara.
Danima's Map
It's not a regular map.
It can gather all the sen of all the Masarians
And project it in a single attack
Only a true Hakuru can do it
Inhabitants of Masara!
Yes you have suffered, and you are scared
But I need you to transfer your Sen Energy to me
Do it for Danima!
For Masara!
But above all. Do it for each other
Because only by joining our forces
Will we win
Let's go, Masarians!
Nero-Sen Fusion!
Goodbye, Sidmodius!
We won....
We won!
Guys! Something bad has happened
Tampo! What happend?
The old portal has stopped working
You can only go back through the hole that the
Chronan-Yatt opened to transport the
Yaquis
The problem is that
What?!
It's closing.
There it is!
Bye, guys! We will not forget you
Quickly! These wings are not going to last much longer
It's Lon!
Lon! We gotta get out of here!
Get away from me!
Lon, you have to
come with us or you will be
trapped in the past
Let go of the helmet and give me your other hand!
You're still our friend, Lon!
I'm not Lon anymore...
No!
We have to get out of here!
The portal is gonna close!
Let's use the Fusion to open it!
Zack! How are we going to go through the portal while using the Fusion?
You need to make the best decision for your team
Even if it's not the best for you
Guys! Go through! I'll stay here and keep it open
But-But what about you?
Don't worry about me, I'll follow you
Where are Zack and Chloe?!
Chloe!
But how are you going to follow us
If you're stuck here keeping it open?
You lied to us!
We're going to sacrifice you
No!
You have to go back to earth!
I don'tcare about earth and I don't care that you don't feel the same for me that I feel for you
But I can't leave you
Chloe! You have to get out of here!
If anything happens to you I will never forgive myself
Because...
why
Because I...
I love you
Duo-Sen Lightning Bolt!
Yeah, me too
way to meet them. Don't
Hey, don't lie!
If the four of us see each other every day,
Yeah, but today you're both going to the movies without us
We've this appointment pending for a long time
See you at the exit.
Let's go for a walk on the beach.
Remember me never to fall in love
always be tough, if deep down
you're a romantic,
you think we'll like it because you say it,
well, I like video games and
you like art and things like that, we're so
indifferent, wait
a minute, are you talking about the movie
or are you?  talking about callao and enjoy
the movie
[Music]
wow it was incredible
you saw the chase and the end
all those things exploding with a pub
and what can you say about the photography and the
script the characters their stories
I loved it ha  been exciting
[Music]
well damn
[Applause]
although I waited for this moment for
millions of years
yes
glock
[Music]
come with me you have
put me in multiple
[Applause]
[Music]
and so the story of the warriors in
tokai came to  Its end
and that it was conquered in June,
the story of Fac and
Chloe continues and they lived adventures so
incredible that we couldn't believe them,
but if you really want to know more
you will have to wish for it with all your
might
i
[Music]